BGM
It's time for another episode of Upcamin, this time with Shiori Yagi of Tsubaki Factory and Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume・24.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Yagi, went to an eyebrow salon to have my eyebrows trimmed.
I'm Yagi, and I'd like to talk about my eyebrow trimming and eyelash perm.
I went to an eyebrow salon and had my eyebrows shaped.
I also had my eyelashes permed.
Then, it really made my makeup easier.
It saves me a lot of time when I do my makeup.
I can get it done in a shorter amount of time.
Even though the time is shortened, the eyelashes don't fall off as easily.
So I'm really glad we did this.
It's really hot this time of year, and you sweat a lot, and sometimes your eyelashes fall off.
I've never tried eyelash power before, but I'm really interested in it.
I've never tried eyelash power before, but I'm very curious about it.
I don't have bangs, so I'm also interested in an eyebrow salon.
That's a great discovery!
I'm looking forward to seeing you in action.
Thank you very much.
I, Sakurai...
It's a little while ago, but...
We have new rehearsal clothes.
When we rehearse, we always wear our lesson clothes
We always rehearse in our lesson clothes, but
We used to wear simple T-shirts and simple pants.
I decided to try on a new rehearsal wear that matches my skeletal structure.
I have a skeletal wave.
I have a skeletal wave bone structure, and I found out that cargo pants, pants that are a little loose, look good on a skeletal wave person.
I bought a lot of cargo pants, and I also bought short tops that would give a good silhouette to my upper body.
I bought a lot of cargo pants and short tops that showed off my upper body silhouette, and when I started rehearsing with them, I thought that my silhouette looked much better in the mirror.
I think it makes rehearsals more enjoyable.
I also have a skeletal wave.
We're the same.
I'm going to try to incorporate it into my hair.
I think it will make your silhouette look really good.
I see.
I'd recommend cargo pants.
I'm going to get some.
We're at HaloCon together right now.
I think they might be similar.
Let's match them for sure.
Let's do it.
Yay!
Okay, let's start with this one.
Yes, ma'am.
Making of Morning Musume。24最強 music video shooting
Morning Musume。24's latest single will be released on August 14.
Here's a look at the making of the shooting of the strongest music video from Morning Musume。 24's latest single.
re Eroon.
Hope it's cool.
Yes yes yes yes
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Sometimes at night, you can fool me
I don't want to hug you for nothing
You don't want to do things that don't change
No more crying, no more tears
Even if it hurts
I'm shining, I'm loving, I'm having fun, I'm harmazer
I mean it so much that I lose my temper, I'm weak in love
I'm weak in love, I'm weak in love, I'm weak in love, I'm weak in love, I'm weak in love
I can't get it out of my hand, I've had enough, I've noticed
I'm thinking black and white and a little cool cool cool theme this time
I'm gonna have a lot of fun with the lipstick.
I hope I can show you the cool side of me, too.
I'm going to work hard today.
I can't pretend to be weak, I'm tired of pretending to be weak.
I can't pretend to be weak, I'm tired of it, bye bye
I don't care if you cry from behind
Me, my time, Ozaki, you're in my way, stop it!
Potty, the strongest, the most clumsy.
I can't pretend to be stupid if I can't get through this big situation
If you go out with me, diamonds, I'd rather love you than be serious or rabbittai
Always Icon Whisking My Bees
You're the dumbest idiot I've ever met.
That's not true.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Sideways.
Time...
Yes, sir.
Let's go then.
Thank you very much.
Okay, we'll go live now.
321.
Yes, sir.
Three twenty-one.
Okay, we're ready for this group.
I'd like you to start by looking away and then look back in.
Okay.
Repeat the song.
That's it. One step forward.
Strongest. Strongest.
By all means, strongest.
Miso
Faith.
The times are pretty expresive, but
But it's not scary at all
Anybody like it pretty hard
I'm the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's the one who's
Jelly Jelly Jelly
We can make it, we can make it
Ruikki, Mimmon, you're right
My sisters
Go for it
It's all Ming-Mong's face.
That was strong.
Here we go.
Yes, sir.
Then I got this. Thank you very much.
Music
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
Now, Mr. Honma, please.
Music
Um, in the middle...
I looked in front of the stage to see where the light was coming from.
But there was no light, so they used some kind of projector to light it from right above.
It was cool.
I used it during the song.
The choreography after the song was really cool.
I know it's not on the schedule, but I wish they would use it.
It was cool.
Yes, we're in the middle of shooting an image scene for a music video.
We have a white set with a light and a frame, and we're dancing in the frame.
This is the third single I've participated in, and I really like the way they used light in a way that I haven't seen before.
I'm really looking forward to the filming.
I hope that when you see the finished film, you can look at this image and think, "This is the place.
Okay, please press the camera.
Yes, cut!
Yes, thank you very much.
Okay, please wait.
Laughs
Levitating
Calm down, И poke failure.
Then we're on the air.
Please wait.
Yes, please. Music, please.
Music.
Yes, cut.
Yes, please.
Music.
Everybody, let's try the club.
Five, six, seven, eight.
MUSIC
Yes, well, I'm going to go into the compine.
Music
music
Not at all. You're just getting started.
I'm going to dodge it.
Don't be afraid to let your guard down
Don't pile it on
It's supposed to be brilliant.
I mean, I can't take it anymore.
I know you're aware of that.
I know you're still clinging to me.
I'll still be me.
You can do it from your body.
I'm the best of the best today...
Lately.
Pretending to be weak.
Next time I'm tired of fighting.
That look on your face, if you want me to notice.
You're right. I don't like it.
I don't like you.
You're the best.
Lately.
Pretending to be an idiot...
It's still up for grabs.
Strongest.
I hate it when people who love me go for it.
Love hurts more than the city
I always be my dream
Strongest fool
The shooting of the strongest music video is over!
Thank you for your hard work.
How was it?
How was it, Mr. Furuya?
Well, it was pretty good.
It's a cool song, and I was careful not to smile during the lip scene.
What about you, Migeta?
I had a hard time with the lip scene too, but I think I was able to show a new side to the songs that I have been doing with a smile on my face.
It was so cool to see everyone standing on stage in parts and singing solo parts only, or two people singing in unison, so I would be happy if you could watch the performance.
I hope you will see it a lot.
I hope you will watch it a lot.
I just watched the VTR, and I thought the strongest part was a very strong song, and the pitch is very difficult.
It's very difficult to find the right pitch.
When I heard it for the first time, it was quite difficult to use the right pitch, and all the members struggled with it.
The first performance was at the Nippon Budokan.
It was the first performance at the Nippon Budokan. We made time to practice singing only during the rehearsals for the Nippon Budokan concert, and we put a lot of effort into both dancing and singing.
We put a lot of effort into both the dance and the song, and we all worked hard to get it just right.
I hope you will listen to the song as well as the music video.
The dance scene in the music video is impressive, isn't it? There are a lot of dance scenes in the music video.
And the dancing is really well coordinated.
I thought, "That's what Morning Musume is all about.
There's something I like about this song.
I really like the part in the B melody where they put layers of lame powder on top of each other to hide their swollen eyelids.
I really like the part of the B melody
I love the part of the B melody where she says, "Overlapping lame powder hides my swollen eyelids.
I think it's great that there's a little cute point in the cool song.
I think it's really cool and I love it!
The lame powder is cute, isn't it?
So cute!
Today, too...
It's amazing.
Yes, it is.
My eyes are puffy.
No, you don't.
So I put on a layer of concealer.
Put some lame powder on it.
Yes, sir.
That's great.
It's the best.
Thank you very much.
Sakurai, you're the best.
This is the making of Morning Musume。24最強 music video shoot.
Hello! Project New Member Audition 2024
Hello! Project, now in its 27th year, is looking for new members!
Every member of Hello!
It is an audition!
The important thing is to have the courage to take the first step
We will do our best to support your first step!
This time, we will hold auditions in two categories
If you love singing, dancing, and Hello Project!
If you love Hello Project, you can audition in Hello Project category.
And for those of you who want to show off your skills and personality in addition to singing and dancing
If you want to show off your skills and personality in addition to singing and dancing, you can apply for the BEYONDS Potential Division.
Why don't you join us and make your dreams come true at Hello Project?
We look forward to hearing from you!
Thank you for watching!
You can do it!
Next, here we go!
Angulum SENQUE HELLO GOODBYE Vocal Recording
From Angulum's latest single
SENQUE HELLO GOODBYE... from Angulum's newest single, SENQUE HELLO GOODBYE.
Okay, I guess I'll come out then.
Okay, I'll go to Emel first.
Up to the point where there aren't just four songs.
The answer I've been searching for, the dream I've always longed for.
The moment I grasped it, something popped.
I should have known that one day this day would come.
Goodbye. I can't chew the sound of that.
Let's see...
I was wondering if I could try it out once.
I was wondering if you could give it a try.
I'm just trying to get a feel for it.
Just a little bit.
Just a light smile.
It'll make you look funny.
Don't look at it.
Just smile a little bit.
So, let's give it a shot.
The answer I've been looking for The dream I've been longing for
The moment I got it, something just popped.
I should have known that one day this would happen
Good-bye, I can't bite the sound of it
It was so good. It's too bad.
You're sure it's here?
Just there. It's too bad.
Why?
Haoi?
Let's just do it there.
Yeah, okay, okay.
Let's do it.
Hearts as hot as glass, hearts as fragile as glass
I think of all the times we believed in each other until today
Let's do it, let's do it.
I can't bite that sound. I can't break it.
♪ Hearts as fragile as glass, connecting
I think of all the times we believed in each other before today.
If I tried to trace the pitch too closely, I'd end up sounding like a wail,
So, please take it all in the atmosphere of the song or something.
At the end,
I'm thinking of Ataki
I hope you sing the last part of the song like "I'm thinking of Ataki," too.
Yes, yes.
While connecting hearts as fragile as glass
I think of the time we believed in each other until today
OK!
Okay, let's get rusty!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Okay.
Okay, rustle number one.
Tears don't suit you. Wave your hands.
Shall we sing until "Ikuyo"?
Yes.
So, let's sing "Thank you," "Hello," and "Good bye" a little later.
Looking up at the same sky, blown by the same wind, we've shared smiles and pain.
Now the light is shining on our respective paths, and it's time for us to start our journey.
Tears don't suit me I'll wave to you Thank you Hello Goodbye
I told you not to sing Hello Goodbye earlier.
Why did you sing it?
It's so good.
But, "Thank you. Hello. Good bye. Shall I take one more shot from the heart?
Please do.
OK, last one then!
I'll wave Thank you, hello, goodbye
Thank you, hello, goodbye
Three times in a row!
Yes, sir!
It's time to go to town Tears don't suit me
I'll wave to you Thank you, hello, goodbye
Okay, okay!
Okay, next! Thank you, hello, goodbye!
OK. Let's go to the end.
Thank you for your time.
The end?
The end.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you.
Bye bye.
I've seen the vocal recording of Ms. Rikako Sasaki.
It's a great song, isn't it?
It's really lovely.
As it is a single for Ms. Sasaki's graduation
The lyrics are in line with her graduation.
I went to see the graduation ceremony of Ms. Mikako Sasaki at Yokohama Arena.
I was able to go to see her graduation ceremony at Yokohama Arena.
I was moved by the memory of that time.
I thought the song was very easy to listen to.
The chorus of the song is very hummable.
I also like this song very much.
I also thought that Ms. Sasaki was really stylish and cute in a moment.
I thought she was very stylish and cute.
I also thought the recording session was very nice.
I was able to watch the recording of the song while thinking how wonderful it was.
That's all for the recording of Rikako Sasaki's vocal for Angstrom Thank you Hello Goodbye.
That's all for the recording of Rikako Sasaki's vocals.
Thanks for watching!
I'd like to thank Shiori Yagi of Tsubaki Factory and
Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。24 is here.
Here's the next one!
BEYONDS Hook's Law Vocal Recording
From the latest single by BEYONDS
Hook's Law", from the latest single by the BEYONDS.
Okay, let's take some pictures, shall we?
Okay.
Let's start with the A melody.
I want to protect my heart, I want to be strong, I want such power
I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong
I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong
If you make it a little darker, I'll let you listen to it a little more.
Oh...
I want to protect my heart
I want to be strong.
I want to be strong
Shrink down and stay down
What I really wish for
I can tell you what I really want
Danseiday
That's okay.
I'll take this one.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go to B melody.
Yes, sir.
Shrink back
I have a true wish
I can confide in you
Dansei de, dansei de, dansei de, dansei de, dansei de, dansei de
With you, with you, with you, with you, with you, with you, with you, with you, with you, with you, with you, with you
To completion, bye bye bye
Let failure be a springboard
Yeah, I'm almost okay, but let's get a little more rhythm out of it
Dansei de, dansei de, dansei de, dansei de, dansei de, dansei de
I'm pretty good, that OK is pretty sharp.
It's an arrangement...
I'll put a little bit of the song on top of it.
Let's try one more time.
Let failure be a springboard. I have one last request today.
Let failure be a springboard, let it be, let it be, let it be, can I have one?
Let failure be a springboard.
With you and you and you and you and sometimes one bye bye bye to completion
Let it be a spring
Yeah, this is fine.
Okay, let's go to the chorus.
Yes
Perfectly done, bye-bye-bye.
Let the failure be a panel
Bouncin' power!
I want to grow more than I am now
Let's go
Be your
Be yourself
Jump up! All your worries, all your dreams
I want to unleash the power of the inbetweener
Be your, be your, be your, be yourself
I'll pull your hand into the future that no one knows
Epi code KX!
Gold medal power
I'm pulling you in
Watch those two spots.
Let's write it down already.
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye!
Let's go! Be your, be your, be your, be yourself!
Be your, be your, be your, be yourself!
Jump up! All my worries, all my dreams
I want to unleash my hidden power
Be your, be your, be your, be your, be yourself!
I'll pull your hand into the future that no one knows
Effikol cake!
Okay, I'll just have a line of HIMETAL POWER.
Yes, sir.
Jump up, all your worries
Dream on
Himmetal power
I want to unleash it
Let's go
OK, we're good to go!
Let's go for a half-car!
Let's go beyond, beyond, beyond, beyond, beyond, beyond, beyond, beyond, beyond, beyond
The sound I want to convey is Let's go beyond, beyond, beyond, be yourself
You just haven't found it yet Your own strong ballet
Aaaaaaand let's have a solid crescendo...
And then we'll move on to the next one.
And, you know, the words to the headline hook line
A little more bounce
Stretch the la...
Hook line words
Hook line word.
The "a" might not be in the right place.
Hook line words
Yes, stretch out with the "la".
Bounce in.
Hook line
Hook line words
Yes, yes, yes, yes
If I'm a little careful there, I'll give it one more try Yes
Hook line words The sound I want to convey is
Let's go beyond, beyond
Be your self
You just haven't found it yet
Your own strong spring
huh?
I've got it in me
Yes, the end!
Thank you for your hard work.
I thought it was a great song from the first time I heard it, and now that I've seen how it was recorded, I think it's a very high value song.
The music video was also very nice, wasn't it?
The music video was also very nice.
I'm a fan of Ms. Miyawane's music video, and I've watched it over and over again.
And isn't Ms. Kobayashi's singing voice in this VTR so wonderful?
It's super nice!
I think your voice has such a beautiful sound.
I totally understand!
I really do.
That's why it was so much fun to hear you sing so much!
It was a lot of fun!
That's all for BEYONDZ, the law of good fortune, Honoka Kobayashi's vocal recording.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for your work!
Shiori Yagi and Rio Sakurai have sent you
It's time to say goodbye to Apkami!
Well, we've watched a lot of videos this time, but I, Sakurai, was impressed by the making of Morning Musume・24's strongest music video, which is our own group.
I was reminded once again of how things were back then, and the way the music video was shot on camera, there were so many shadows and light effects.
I am very happy if you could watch the making of the music video and see what it was like when you were watching it.
And on August 14, we'll be releasing the two A-sides of "Sentimental Songs of Time" and "The Strongest Song of All", so please be sure to check them out!
I, Yagi, was very impressed with the vocal recording of Rikako Sasaki's song "SENQUE HELLO GOODBYE".
Actually, this recording was her last recording as Angulum.
That's why it's hard to imagine
I was very happy to see Ms. Sasaki's mischievous side and her sincere attitude toward her songs and her slightly husky voice. We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production process of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel to get a glimpse of what you don't normally see.
This time, our partners are Shiori Yagi of Tsubaki Factory and Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume・24.
Good bye.
Next time on Apkami!
Morning Musume。24's song at the time of "Somewhat Sentimental
The making of music video shooting
And
JuiceJuice: Recording of "LOVE for something that doesn't exist" will be shown on the website.
Please look forward to it!